Now, I'm going to go over using
现在我将介绍如何使用
a normal distribution for selecting initial model weights.
正态分布选择初始模型权重
So again, well first visualize what this looks like using NumPy and a histogram.
首先 我将使用 NumPy 和直方图进行可视化
This time, I'm using np.random.normal.
这次我将使用np.random.normal
This, instead of taking in a low and
此函数接受的是
a high range of values like the uniform distribution,
均值和标准差
takes in a mean and a standard deviation.
而不像均匀分布那样接受上下限
If a mean and standard deviation are not specified as they weren't here,
如果均值和标准差没有指定 就像这里一样
the defaults are zero and a standard deviation of one.
则默认情况下 均值是 0 标准差是 1
So, I'm telling it for a mean of zero and a standard deviation of one,
这里表示创建 1000 个值 其中均值为 0
to create 1,000 values.
标准差为 1
Now, the mean should just be the average of all these values, the center value.
均值是指所有这些值的平均值
The standard deviation represents the spread of values around that mean.
标准差表示值在均值周围的分散程度
You can see here, what a normal distribution looks like
此图显示了均值为 0
for a mean of zero and a standard deviation of one.
标准差为 1 的正态分布的分布效果
Most of the values are concentrated in this range.
大多数值在此范围内比较集中
Again, we're using histograms.
我们使用的是直方图
So, we've bucketed 1,000 values into 500 buckets.
因此将 1000 个值分成了 500 个区间
In the uniform case, the values were pre-evenly distributed along the range,
在均匀分布中 值在范围内提前均匀地分布
and they fell about two values to a bucket.
一个区间大约有两个值
Here, a normal distribution has most values collected near their mean, zero.
而在正态分布中 大多数值都靠近均值 0
The histogram itself looks like a curve that shows
直方图本身看起来像一条曲线
how values fall within a standard deviation of the mean.
表示值在均值的一个标准差内如何分布
So, if we select our initial model weight values from this kind of distribution,
如果我们从这种分布里选择初始模型权重值
we'll get random values that are generally closer to
那么所选的随机值通常比从均匀分布里选择的值
zero than if we selected from a uniform distribution.
更加接近 0
Picking small weight values,
一开始选择很小的权重值
initially, may offer some benefits.
可能会带来一些好处
In fact, I'm going to leave this as an exercise for you
这部分我将布置成练习
since you've seen a number of examples of weight initialization already.
因为你已经见过很多权重初始化示例
I want you to define an initialization function,
因此我将要求你定义一个初始化函数
then initialize the weights in every layer of
然后通过从正态分布里取样
our model by sampling from a normal distribution.
初始化每个层级的权重
The distribution should still follow our general rule;
分布应该依然遵守一般法则
it should have a mean of zero and a standard deviation that's equal to
均值为 0 标准差等于 1/√n￣
one over the square root of n. Once you complete this function,
完成这个函数后
I want you to compare a few different models.
请比较几个模型
Compare weights with uniform initialization and normal initialization.
比较均匀初始化权重和正态初始化权重
Finally, I want you to create a third model,
最后创建第三个模型
one without any explicit weight initialization.
它没有明确的权重初始化方式
Take a look at how these three models compare,
看看这三个模型的比较结果
and next, I'll show you my implementation.
接下来我将演示我的实现代码